Our neighbor was trying to get the cats in her backyard fixed,
but she couldn't find a low-cost spay-neuter appointment, so those cats had more cats.
Cats in the street or in overcrowded shelters are symptoms of an equity problem.
50% of pet-owning households in the U.S. can no longer afford a basic vet visit.
And this lack of affordable services disproportionately impacts families right here in New York,
particularly low-income pet owners and communities of color.
That's why we're building a brand new non-profit veterinary clinic in Brooklyn,
and we need your help to get the doors open.
This isn't just an idea. We're finishing construction right now.
We need your support to complete the build-out, purchase remaining medical equipment,
hire the rest of our veterinary team,
and make these critical services available and affordable to thousands of New Yorkers for years to come.
Your generosity will help give more cats the life they all deserve
and more families the chance to enjoy the love and companionship that our pets provide.
We're so close to opening our doors, but only you can help us take the final steps.
Please donate today.